verveindia.com 2013-03-03

# 

###  What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you fill out a form or lioneljeshuran@gmail.com.   
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number or company name. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.   

### What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
To send periodic emails   
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.   

### How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.   
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.   
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.   

### Do we use cookies? 

We do not use cookies.   

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.   

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.   
lioneljeshuran@gmail.com   
lioneljeshuran@gmail.com   

### Online Privacy Policy Only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.   
Your Consent   
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.   
Changes to our Privacy Policy   

### If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 02-Aug-2011   

### Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   
http://www.verveindia.com   
6 Dhanammal St., Spurtank Road, Chetpet   
Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600 031   
India   
lionel@verveindia.com
